skygolf.com 2005-12-18

# SkyGolf - Privacy Policy

**You Are Here:** Home > **Privacy**

At SkyHawke Technologies, LLC, ("SkyHawke"), we are committed to protecting the privacy of the information you provide to us. All of the information we collect about you is strictly used to process your orders, secure and maintain your SkyPlayer™ course storage data, and provide a convenient, personalized shopping and product use experience. Please read the additional information below for more details about our privacy policy.

* * *

What information do we collect and how do we use it?  
How does the SkyGolf website protect customer information?  
Will SkyGolf disclose the information it collects to outside parties?  
How does the SkyGolf website allow customers to update or change the information it collects?   
How does SkyGolf protect the privacy of children younger than 13?   
Your consent 

* * *

**What information do we collect and how do we use it?**

When you register your SkyGolf® product electronically, we obtain and store your product's electronic serial number, your name, mailing address, shipping address, e-mail address, user name and password, telephone number, and optional information you voluntarily submit to us, such as age range, the places you go on vacation, and how many times a year you go on vacation. This allows us to properly register your product, maintain an account for you on our website, www.skygolfgps.com, and provide access to your SkyCourse data, and to issue you a unique registration code. It also helps us provide you with premium customer support.

When you place an order, we obtain and store your name, shipping address, billing address, e-mail address, a password, and a password hint (in the event you forget your password). This allows us to authorize you to obtain software updates, downloads and allows us should you select an Annual Skyplayer™ membership subscription to establish your SkyFolders™ and SkyCourse™ storage information on our web site.

For electronic purchases you make on our website, a secured third-party financial institution will request and manage your payment and personal identifying information to authorize billing charges to be posted to your credit card account. Except for customers who subscribe to an Annual SkyPlayer™ Membership Plan, SkyHawke does not capture or retain your electronic payment information, such as credit card account information. For all electronic merchandise purchases from our web site, SkyHawke temporarily retains the credit card data and personal identification information in a highly secured, encrypted electronic format only long enough to authorize your credit card to be charged using a secure third party financial institution, and your order processed. 

For those customers who subscribe via our website, www.skygolfgps.com, to an Annual SkyPlayer™ Membership Plan, _we do retain certain portions of your electronic payment data for use only for subscription renewal purposes_ , and _only_ in an off-line, highly secured, encrypted, machine readable only (non-readable by human eyes) format. 

For non-electronic purchases you make via facsimile or telephone, and you provide us your credit card data and personal identifying information to authorize billing charges to be posted to your credit card account, SkyHawke temporarily retains the credit card data and personal identification information only long enough to authorize your credit card to be charged using a secure third party financial institution, and your order processed. While SkyHawke has this information in it's possession, your payment and personal identification information is carefully secured so that only authorized SkyHawke personnel have access to and use of this information. After processing your order, your payment and personal identification information is securely purged and is not retained by SkyHawke.

When you submit a support question online, we request and retain only your name and e-mail address. This allows us to promptly address your issue and communicate our response to you via e-mail.

Top

**How does the SkyGolf website protect customer information?**

The SkyGolf website uses the latest web security and encryption technology to keep your personal information safe. All your ordering information — including your name and address — is encrypted using a secure server for maximum security.

For Annual SkyPlayer™ Membership Plans and _only_ for the use for renewal subscription purposes, _we do retain certain portions of your electronic payment data_ , and _only_ in an off-line, highly secured, encrypted, machine readable only (non-readable by human eyes) format. For all other electronic purchases, a secure third-party financial institution receives and manages your credit card number and other personal identifying information only to verify the credit card number and process transactions. SkyHawke never retains any credit information on any of it's _on-line_ servers. When making electronic purchases, we are simply notified by the secured third party financial institution as to whether your credit card transaction is approved or declined. 

If you do not want to submit your purchase information online, you may call our Customer Service department at 1.888.SKYGOLF (888.759.4653) to submit your order and credit card information. Our representatives are available from 8:00 a.m. to 5:00 p.m. CST Monday through Friday. 

Top

**Will SkyGolf disclose the information it collects to outside parties?**

No. The information we collect from you is used to service your account with us. The only time SkyGolf GPS may release account information is if we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to (i) comply with any mandates from governmental authorities, (ii) comply with any laws, (iii) enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements, or (iv) protect the rights, property, or safety of the SkyGolf website, our users, or others.

Top

**How does the SkyGolf website allow customers to update or change the information it collects?**

If at any time you would like to change any information in your account, you may update your account information on our website by logging on with your user name and password, you may e-mail your changes to us at [customerservice@skygolfgps.com](mailto:customerservice@skygolfgps.com) , or you may call our Customer Service department during normal business hours. In order for us to process your changes, we must be able to verify your sending email address as your registered email address on our web site. For security reasons, you must also provide us your website user name only in any correspondence to authorize any changes. PLEASE DO NOT PLACE YOUR PASSWORD INFORMATION IN AN EMAIL TO US! A customer service representative will verify your authorization and process your changes as soon as possible. For renewals of our Annual SkyPlayer™ Membership Plans, you may update your electronic payment information at the time of renewal, which is maintained off-line in a highly secured, encrypted, machine readable format only. 

Top

**How does SkyGolf protect the privacy of children younger than 13?**

SkyGolf is concerned about the privacy of young children and does not knowingly collect any personal information from a child under 13. We suggest that you become involved with your child's access to the Internet and to our site to ensure that his or her privacy is well protected.

Top

**Your consent**

By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of this information by SkyGolf . If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please contact our Customer Service department from our Contact webpage or at (601) 605-6100.

Top

**back to previous page**

©2001-2005 [SkyHawke Technologies, LLC.](http://www.skyhawke.com/) All Rights Reserved.
